<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CTF on Morgan&#39;s Cyber Security Shed of Chaos</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ctfs/ctf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CTF on Morgan&#39;s Cyber Security Shed of Chaos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/ctfs/ctf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mr Robot - Boot2Root CTF Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://example.com/ctfs/mr-robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/ctfs/mr-robot/</guid>
      <description>Mr Robot CTF Walk-through Network Enumeration and Scanning Website Navigation CTF Flags Flag 1 Flag 2 Flag 3 Mr Robot CTF Walk-through Network Enumeration and Scanning The first we must do before we do anything we must scan the virtual network. Use arp-net to scan the virtual network. Then a list of the IP addresses should appear. One of the devices on the network should have “PCS Systemtechnik GmbH” as the vendor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Robot - Boot2Root CTF Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://example.com/programming/mr-robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/programming/mr-robot/</guid>
      <description>Mr Robot CTF Walk-through Network Enumeration and Scanning Website Navigation CTF Flags Flag 1 Flag 2 Flag 3 Mr Robot CTF Walk-through Network Enumeration and Scanning The first we must do before we do anything we must scan the virtual network. Use arp-net to scan the virtual network. Then a list of the IP addresses should appear. One of the devices on the network should have “PCS Systemtechnik GmbH” as the vendor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TryHackMe Introduction CTF - (Originally written for the members of the USWCSS.)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/ctfs/intro-thm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/ctfs/intro-thm/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hello welcome to our introduction CTF. This CTF is to give you an idea of how does ethical hacking works within a CTF environment. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what a CTF, a CTF is basically a exercise/game in which &amp;ldquo;flag&amp;rdquo; are hidden within purposefully-vulnerable programs or websites. A CTF flag would look something &amp;ldquo;CTF{g3t_g00d_n00b2}&amp;rdquo; and would be hidden within a root/admin folder. There are multiple types of CTFs such as: Forensic CTFs (which utilities digital forensics), Web CTFs where the attacker attacks a web server (which is what we will be covering today), Reverse Engineering (which involve exploiting a program binary), etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
